<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>A phanatick play. The first part, as it was presented before and by the Lord Fleetwood, Sir Arthur Hasilrig, Sir Henry Vane, the Lord Lambert, and others, last night, with master jester and master pudding.</title>
         </titleStmt>
         <editionStmt>
            <edition>
               <date>1660</date>
            </edition>
         </editionStmt>
         <extent>Approx. 13 KB of XML-encoded text transcribed from 5 1-bit group-IV TIFF page images.</extent>
         <publicationStmt>
            <publisher>Text Creation Partnership,</publisher>
            <pubPlace>Ann Arbor, MI ; Oxford (UK) :</pubPlace>
            <date when="2014-11">2014-11 (EEBO-TCP Phase 2).</date>
            <idno type="DLPS">A85104</idno>
            <idno type="STC">Wing F397</idno>
            <idno type="STC">Thomason E1017_10</idno>
            <idno type="STC">ESTC R207965</idno>
            <idno type="EEBO-CITATION">99866978</idno>
            <idno type="PROQUEST">99866978</idno>
            <idno type="VID">119268</idno>
            <availability>
               <p>To the extent possible under law, the Text Creation Partnership has waived all copyright and related or neighboring rights to this keyboarded and encoded edition of the work described above, according to the terms of the CC0 1.0 Public Domain Dedication (http://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/). This waiver does not extend to any page images or other supplementary files associated with this work, which may be protected by copyright or other license restrictions. Please go to https://www.textcreationpartnership.org/ for more information about the project.</p>
            </availability>
         </publicationStmt>
         <seriesStmt>
            <title>Early English books online text creation partnership.</title>
         </seriesStmt>
         <notesStmt>
            <note>(EEBO-TCP ; phase 2, no. A85104)</note>
            <note>Transcribed from: (Early English Books Online ; image set 119268)</note>
            <note>Images scanned from microfilm: (Thomason Tracts ; 151:E1017[10])</note>
         </notesStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <biblFull>
               <titleStmt>
                  <title>A phanatick play. The first part, as it was presented before and by the Lord Fleetwood, Sir Arthur Hasilrig, Sir Henry Vane, the Lord Lambert, and others, last night, with master jester and master pudding.</title>
               </titleStmt>
               <editionStmt>
                  <edition>This is the first edition.</edition>
               </editionStmt>
               <extent>[2], 6 p.   </extent>
               <publicationStmt>
                  <publisher>[s.n.],</publisher>
                  <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
                  <date>printed in the year, 1660.</date>
               </publicationStmt>
               <notesStmt>
                  <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "March. 14 1659"; also the last two numbers of the imprint date have been marked through.</note>
                  <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
               </notesStmt>
            </biblFull>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
      <encodingDesc>
         <projectDesc>
            <p>Created by converting TCP files to TEI P5 using tcp2tei.xsl,
      TEI @ Oxford.
      </p>
         </projectDesc>
         <editorialDecl>
            <p>EEBO-TCP is a partnership between the Universities of Michigan and Oxford and the publisher ProQuest to create accurately transcribed and encoded texts based on the image sets published by ProQuest via their Early English Books Online (EEBO) database (http://eebo.chadwyck.com). The general aim of EEBO-TCP is to encode one copy (usually the first edition) of every monographic English-language title published between 1473 and 1700 available in EEBO.</p>
            <p>EEBO-TCP aimed to produce large quantities of textual data within the usual project restraints of time and funding, and therefore chose to create diplomatic transcriptions (as opposed to critical editions) with light-touch, mainly structural encoding based on the Text Encoding Initiative (http://www.tei-c.org).</p>
            <p>The EEBO-TCP project was divided into two phases. The 25,368 texts created during Phase 1 of the project (2000-2009), initially available only to institutions that contributed to their creation, were released into the public domain on 1 January 2015. The approximately 40,000 texts produced during Phase 2 (2009- ), of which 34,963 had been released as of 2020, originally similarly restricted, were similarly freed from all restrictions on 1 August 2020. As of that date anyone is free to take and use these texts for any purpose (modify them, annotate them, distribute them, etc.). But we do respectfully request that due credit and attribution be given to their original source.</p>
            <p>Users should be aware of the process of creating the TCP texts, and therefore of any assumptions that can be made about the data.</p>
            <p>Text selection was based on the New Cambridge Bibliography of English Literature (NCBEL). If an author (or for an anonymous work, the title) appears in NCBEL, then their works are eligible for inclusion. Selection was intended to range over a wide variety of subject areas, to reflect the true nature of the print record of the period. In general, first editions of a works in English were prioritized, although there are a number of works in other languages, notably Latin and Welsh, included and sometimes a second or later edition of a work was chosen if there was a compelling reason to do so.</p>
            <p>Image sets were sent to external keying companies for transcription and basic encoding. Quality assurance was then carried out by editorial teams in Oxford and Michigan. 5% (or 5 pages, whichever is the greater) of each text was proofread for accuracy and those which did not meet QA standards were returned to the keyers to be redone. After proofreading, the encoding was enhanced and/or corrected and characters marked as illegible were corrected where possible up to a limit of 100 instances per text. Any remaining illegibles were encoded as &lt;gap&gt;s. Understanding these processes should make clear that, while the overall quality of TCP data is very good, some errors will remain and some readable characters will be marked as illegible. Users should bear in mind that in all likelihood such instances will never have been looked at by a TCP editor.</p>
            <p>The texts were encoded and linked to page images in accordance with level 4 of the TEI in Libraries guidelines.</p>
            <p>Copies of the texts have been issued variously as SGML (TCP schema; ASCII text with mnemonic sdata character entities); displayable XML (TCP schema; characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or text strings within braces); or lossless XML (TEI P5, characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or TEI g elements).</p>
            <p>Keying and markup guidelines are available at the <ref target="http://www.textcreationpartnership.org/docs/.">Text Creation Partnership web site</ref>.</p>
         </editorialDecl>
         <listPrefixDef>
            <prefixDef ident="tcp"
                       matchPattern="([0-9\-]+):([0-9IVX]+)"
                       replacementPattern="http://eebo.chadwyck.com/downloadtiff?vid=$1&amp;page=$2"/>
            <prefixDef ident="char"
                       matchPattern="(.+)"
                       replacementPattern="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/textcreationpartnership/Texts/master/tcpchars.xml#$1"/>
         </listPrefixDef>
      </encodingDesc>
      <profileDesc>
         <langUsage>
            <language ident="eng">eng</language>
         </langUsage>
         <textClass>
            <keywords scheme="http://authorities.loc.gov/">
               <term>Political satire, English --  17th Century.</term>
               <term>Great Britain --  Politics and government --  1649-1660 --  Humor --  Early works to 1800.</term>
            </keywords>
         </textClass>
      </profileDesc>
      <revisionDesc>
         <change>
            <date>2012-08</date>
            <label>TCP</label>Assigned for keying and markup</change>
         <change>
            <date>2012-08</date>
            <label>SPi Global</label>Keyed and coded from ProQuest page images</change>
         <change>
            <date>2013-03</date>
            <label>Mona Logarbo</label>Sampled and proofread</change>
         <change>
            <date>2013-03</date>
            <label>Mona Logarbo</label>Text and markup reviewed and edited</change>
         <change>
            <date>2014-03</date>
            <label>pfs</label>Batch review (QC) and XML conversion</change>
      </revisionDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text xml:lang="eng">
      <front>
         <div type="title_page">
            <pb facs="tcp:119268:1" rendition="simple:additions"/>
            <p>A Phanatick PLAY.</p>
            <p>THE FIRST PART, As it was preſented before and by the Lord <hi>Fleetwood,</hi> Sir <hi>Arthur Haſilrig,</hi> Sir <hi>Henry Vane,</hi> the Lord <hi>Lambert,</hi> and others, laſt Night, WITH Maſter <hi>Jeſter</hi> and Maſter <hi>Pudding.</hi>
            </p>
            <p>This is the Firſt Edition.</p>
            <q>
               <l>The Knave the chiefeſt Card hath won the day,</l>
               <l>Had not the <hi>KING</hi> come in whilſt they did Play.</l>
            </q>
            <p>
               <hi>London</hi> Printed in the Year, 166<gap reason="illegible" extent="1 letter">
                  <desc>•</desc>
               </gap>.</p>
         </div>
      </front>
      <body>
         <div type="drama">
            <pb facs="tcp:119268:2"/>
            <pb n="1" facs="tcp:119268:2"/>
            <head>A Phanatique PLAY.</head>
            <stage>Enter a <hi>Jeſter,</hi> and with him a <hi>Jack-Pudding.</hi>
            </stage>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſter.</speaker>
               <p>
                  <seg rend="decorInit">G</seg>Ood Morrow Mr. <hi>Pudding,</hi> how is it now?</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pudding.</speaker>
               <p>Never more at hearts eaſe in all my life.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>What news at <hi>Weſtminſter</hi> to day?</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud</speaker>
               <p>Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, fa, la, la, ha, ha, fa, la.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>Tell me Mr. <hi>Puding</hi> what you laugh at that I may laugh with you and be merry.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <p>I am going to ſee a Play, a new Play af<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ter the old faſhion, that makes me ſo merry.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>But prethee tell me who plays the devils part.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <p>In good truth Sir <hi>Arthur Haſilrigg.</hi>
               </p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>He's full of compunction is he not?</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <p>He hates <hi>Charles Stuart</hi> inveterately, be<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cauſe he has gained a vaſt eſtate of his lands into his hands, and holds it for his own.</p>
            </sp>
            <stage>Enter <hi>Lambert, Haſilrigg</hi> and <hi>Vane.</hi>
            </stage>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſter.</speaker>
               <p>What! my Lord <hi>Lambert,</hi> Sir <hi>Arthur Haſilrigg,</hi> and Sir <hi>Henry Vane,</hi> well met all three of you, whither are all of you bound you go ſo faſt, &amp; want your horſes? what all alike, all alike!</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <pb n="2" facs="tcp:119268:3"/>
               <speaker>Lambert.</speaker>
               <p>I am bound for the Weſt, to viſit Sir <hi>George Booth,</hi> and I hope he will make me wel<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>come; for I hear his Lands are reſtored again, which by my unjuſtneſs was ſequeſtred.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <p>The Divel he wil; he cannot chuſe but make you welcome, with a Fox to you.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Haſl.</speaker>
               <p>Sir, I am going to Portſmouth, for I hope they will entertaine me with all reſpect.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>Thou lookeſt ſo like the Divel that they will raiſe the Bulwarks of the great guns againſt your highneſs.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Vane.</speaker>
               <p>I am bound to my country houſe for my healths ſake, thank the Rump.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <p>I'le turn Doctor, and give you a Scotch pil; fear you not an Apothecary, for I was Moun<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tebanck to <hi>Nol</hi> with the great Noſe; my Pils wrought ſo effectually that they brought him to reſt.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>
                  <hi>Puddings</hi> pils will make you ſhit out your diſeaſe as freely as you was ſhit out of the Rump, your ſelf, and eaſe your diſcontents.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <p>May it pleaſe your honours to play one game at Honours, &amp; I'le furniſh you with Cards?</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>What will you play for <hi>John Lambert.</hi>
               </p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Lamb.</speaker>
               <p>An <hi>Engliſh</hi> Crown if you pleaſe.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <l>Are you all agreed or not?</l>
               <l>All anſwers, We are all agreed.</l>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>I'le deal, <hi>Lambert</hi> do you ſhuffle, and <hi>Pud<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ding</hi> ſhal cut and we'l play the knaves to the pur<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>poſe, to make you all merry.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Haſl.</speaker>
               <p>I like not his cheating play, he Jugles, I'le play no longer, I'le play no longer, by my Bi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſhoprick
<pb n="3" facs="tcp:119268:3"/>of <hi>Durham,</hi> he's a falſe player.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Vane</speaker>
               <p>I'le ſhuffle the Cards my ſelfe.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Lam.</speaker>
               <p>
                  <hi>Vane,</hi> you play Legerdemain under-hand, ſee how he culs out the Knaves, to put them into his own hands, and cheat us all, but we want a fourth man to make up the ſet.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <p>I'le play if you pleaſe.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Lamb.</speaker>
               <p>Not with us, we'l have no fools.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <p>If you had caſt all the knaves then.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Fleetwood.</speaker>
               <l>I'le make a fourth man.</l>
               <l>Are you all greed? yes, yes.</l>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Lamb.</speaker>
               <p>You ſhall be my partner then.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Fleet.</speaker>
               <p>With all my heart, I will, I will.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>Shuffle Gaffer General <hi>Fleetwood.</hi>
               </p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Haſl.</speaker>
               <p>
                  <hi>Vane,</hi> I ſee, muſt of neceſſity be with me, Gaffer <hi>Fleetwood,</hi> you are a cunning Gamſter, and the cheatingeſt player in this Nation, play fair or I will kick you out of the Company.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>Hark, hark, a noiſe, a noiſe!</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <p>What iſt, what iſt, hey, hey, hey,</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>The North wind, it blows ſtrong.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Flhet.</speaker>
               <p>
                  <hi>Lambert</hi> ſhut you the dore, keepe out the wind, riſe and begone, I'le keepe your ſtake, and my own I'le warrant you.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <p>Gaffer <hi>Fleetwood,</hi> thats fowl play, to ſend <hi>Lambert</hi> to ſhut the door whilſt you run away with all the money.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Fleet.</speaker>
               <p>Hold thy tongue, there's half a piece for thee; if any enquire for me, tell them I am gone to the Committee of Safety.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <p>
                  <hi>Lambert</hi> is come again, call them away, to come and play out their game, I ſay.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <pb n="4" facs="tcp:119268:4"/>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>Come all away, come all away, ſit down.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Haſl.</speaker>
               <p>Deal <hi>Fleetwood,</hi> deal <hi>Fleetwood,</hi> why are you ſo ſlow to deal to others, and ſo quick to deal to your ſelf, we all weight upon you?</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Lamb.</speaker>
               <p>I am ſure he ſent me to ſhut the door, and carried away my money inſtead of his own.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>Sirs you doe not make uſe of your time, know not you that the Drums will beat buy and buy, are you mad, make uſe of time, whilſt time is to be had.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <p>Play quick, ſilently, and now play round.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Fleet.</speaker>
               <p>Who dealt, who dealt this round?</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Lamb.</speaker>
               <p>My Lord General <hi>Fleetwood.</hi>
               </p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>If he be all wood, ſound or rotten t'wil burn.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <p>Can you tell whether here or in Hell?</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>He'l have all the whole pack except four.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Haſl.</speaker>
               <p>What four I wiſh for no more—</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>What the Divel ale you <hi>Haſilrig,</hi> blow in my blowing box, and I will ſhew you how to Conjure, command what you pleaſe in your thoughts, it ſhall be performed by your blaſt, blow ſtrong ſweet or ſower.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Haſl.</speaker>
               <p>I have blown ſuch a blaſt; my mind, &amp;c.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <l>By all the vertue in my conjuring books,</l>
               <l>The City Gates are all blown off the hooks.</l>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <l>Your Honours fury to this cities known,</l>
               <l>What would you doe if that it were your own?</l>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Haſl.</speaker>
               <l>The Golden Chains ſhould quickly flye,</l>
               <l>My ſelf would Raign without tranquility.</l>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <l>My mind unto remembrance calls one thing</l>
               <l>That all this time you plaid without a King.</l>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <pb n="5" facs="tcp:119268:4"/>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>Through up your cards, your game is not worth a pin.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <p>Then for a fool I will come in.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>Sir <hi>Arther</hi> many maimed <hi>Souldiers</hi> wait for you.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Arthur,</speaker>
               <p>Let them wait and be hanged.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <p>Speak to them your ſelf, youl pleaſe them.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Haſl.</speaker>
               <p>Who deſires to ſpeak with <hi>Arthur Haſlrig?</hi>
               </p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Souldiers.</speaker>
               <p>Your honours <hi>Souldiers</hi> for their Pen<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tion, we are all in are are fifteen Months.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Haſl.</speaker>
               <p>You are no <hi>Souldiers,</hi> but a pack of rogues.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Soul.</speaker>
               <p>It becomes not your honour to call all <hi>Souldiers</hi> Rogues.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>The Gods confound your honour.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <p>Sir <hi>William Waller</hi> will tell you that you rid the field of your perſon at the <hi>Vize,</hi> or run away, that's plain.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>Play your game or give over.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <p>Sir <hi>Arthur</hi> play <hi>Durham</hi> Biſhoprick, the old quit rents or yearly revenues, was one thou<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſand ſix hundred twenty one pounds eighteen ſhillings and three pence, whereof the Biſhop paid to the King, one hundred ſixty two pounds, two ſhillings ſix pence and odd, beſide Mr. <hi>Colingwoods</hi> lands, and ſeveral Parks and other Lands, which for the company ſake I forbear to name.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt:</speaker>
               <p>Play round a Crown a head boys.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <p>What never a King here to be found?</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Haſl.</speaker>
               <p>I fear he'l be at my hand too ſoon.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Fleet.</speaker>
               <p>Where's the King, in your hand?</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Haſl.</speaker>
               <p>Upon my life I'le keep him out, he ſhall be a King and no King at all, by my conſent.</p>
            </sp>
            <stage>
               <pb n="6" facs="tcp:119268:5"/> Enter a <hi>King,</hi> a <hi>General,</hi> a <hi>Jeſter,</hi> and a <hi>Pudding.</hi>
            </stage>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>Suppoſe they have but <hi>Fleetwood, Lambert, Haſlrig</hi> and <hi>Vane</hi> into a bag, the firſt that comes forth, will be a—what you pleaſe.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <p>Come ſee quickly a fine ſight:</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>Gaffer King, Gaffer King, hear, here they have put <hi>Lambert</hi> and <hi>Haſlrig</hi> into a great Bird-Cage; did you ever ſee the like to this that they have now done?</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <p>They look like two night birds, and ſing moſt melodiouſly, ſhitten ſweetly, the one ſings on this wiſe in the Cage:</p>
               <p>I do deſire <hi>Portſmouth,</hi> once more to ſee.</p>
               <p>The other anſwered.</p>
               <p>I would I was at <hi>Durham</hi> now with thee.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Jeſt.</speaker>
               <p>
                  <hi>Lambert</hi> What have you now in your hat?</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Lamb.</speaker>
               <p>My head yet, ſo long as I can keep it.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Pud.</speaker>
               <p>My Lord, be well adviſed er'e you parr with it.</p>
            </sp>
            <sp>
               <speaker>Lamb.</speaker>
               <l>So I will I'le warrant thee <hi>Pudding.</hi>
               </l>
               <l>They all ſing together.</l>
               <l>Now let us all together rant and ſing,</l>
               <l>Though here be all the knaves, we want the King</l>
               <l>Here may we be and the Countrey not offend,</l>
               <l>Waiting dayly, expecting of our end.</l>
            </sp>
         </div>
         <trailer>FINIS.</trailer>
      </body>
   </text>
</TEI>
